Bridal Wave is a comedy, romance, tv movie film directed by Michael M. Scott.
With her wedding day rapidly approaching, an anxious
bride-to-be has doubts about her pending marriage.
At a romantic island resort, she encounters a handsome kindred spirit and must
now decide if her "perfect" fiancé is really her true love.
Georgie Dwyer, played by Arielle Kebbel.
Luke Griggs, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Felice Hamilton, played by Jaclyn Smith.
Dr. Phillip Hamilton, played by David Haydn-Jones.
Emma, played by Colleen Wheeler.
Judd, played by Daryl Shuttleworth.
Andrew Walker  is a Canadian actor and film producer.
He made his film debut in Laserhawk (1997), followed by roles in American television
series such as Maybe It's Me, Sabrina the Teenage Witch, and Hot Properties.
He also co-starred in Steel Toes (2006), which earned him
an ACTRA Award for Best Actor in 2008.
He subsequently appeared in films such as The Mountie and The Gundown, and had
a starring role on the Lifetime cop drama Against the Wall.
The film explores themes of nurse, resort, wedding, bride-to-be, hallmark.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.